[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What did the developers want to turn the Goon Docks into in the movie The Goonies?", "correct_answer": "Golf Course", "incorrect_answers": ["Amusement Park", "Parking Garage", "Shopping Mall"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where and when does the movie Indiana Jones and the Temple of Doom begin?", "correct_answer": "Shanghai, China 1935", "incorrect_answers": ["Tokyo, Japan 1933", "Singapore, 1937", "Hong Kong, China 1936"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the 1978 film Animal House, the guys from Delta stole the questions to what subject exam out of the trash dumpster?", "correct_answer": "Psychology", "incorrect_answers": ["U.S. History", "American Literature", "Calculus"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these mammals was brought to Australia by humans?", "correct_answer": "The dingo", "incorrect_answers": ["The echidna", "The koala", "The Tasmanian tiger"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many young can an adult badger have at one time?", "correct_answer": "1-5", "incorrect_answers": ["1-8", "just 1", "1-2"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What blood song did Michael Jackson release in 1997?", "correct_answer": "Blood on the Dance Floor", "incorrect_answers": ["Blood on the Bar", "Blood on the Scene", "Blood on My Hands"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which famous British group performs the title song in A View to a Kill?", "correct_answer": "Duran Duran", "incorrect_answers": ["Tears For Fears", "ABC", "Soft Cell"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these statements best describes the mathematical constant  e?", "correct_answer": "It is a transcendental and irrational number.", "incorrect_answers": ["It is a transcendental number.", "It is an algebraic transcendental and irrational number.", "It is a rational transcendental number."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which South American country can the Nazca Lines be found?", "correct_answer": "Peru", "incorrect_answers": ["Boliva", "Chile", "Argentina"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Approximately what is the speed of light in vacuum?", "correct_answer": "300 000 km/s", "incorrect_answers": ["250 000 km/s", "1 000 000 km/s", "12 000 km/s"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Does the condition known as Hypoglycemia imply that blood sugar levels in the body are too high?", "correct_answer": "No", "incorrect_answers": ["Yes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The fear of women is called hierophobia.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]